hancocks-paducah.com 2019-02-12

# Privacy Policy | Hancock’s of Paducah

We created this policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to ensuring your privacy. That's why, when you visit www.hancocks-paducah.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet. If any of your concerns regarding privacy are not addressed here, you can Contact Us with any additional questions. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Internet site.

What information do we collect and how is it used?

Order Processing

When you place an order with us, we need to know your name, mailing address, email address, credit card number, and expiration date in order to process your order and communicate with you regarding the status of your order. We may also use this information to notify you of special offers that we think may be of interest to you. If you are a registered user at **www.hancocks-paducah.com** and do not wish to receive this information, visiting [My Account](https://checkout.hancocks-paducah.com/s.nl?sc=6&sc=6&whence=&origin=myaccount&login=T&vid=BmO4ZSmMAjo91M6m&chrole=17&ck=Ja6bHSmMAjg91FCi&cktime=166953&promocode=&promocodeaction=overwrite&sj=WIIHT4oRV059206TTHkWd6ySF%3B1549993786722&gc=clear) and Selecting Check Sign-In Information to change your preferences. If you are not a registered user, please Contact Us to remove your name from our mailing list.

Gift Orders

If you are ordering a gift that needs to be shipped to an address other than your own, we also need to know the name and address of the gift recipient in order to process and ship the order. This information will be used primarily to fulfill the order and, if necessary, communicate with the gift recipient about the status of the order. The gift recipient or the ship to address will be flagged as such and we do not intend to send promotional materials to such addresses. 

Customer Registration

Our registration form requires customer contact information, which we use to process subsequent orders without asking you to re-enter it. If you choose to register at **www.hancocks-paducah.com** , we require that you provide your name, mailing address, email address, a login name, a password, and a password hint. Optional items requested during the registration process are day and evening telephone numbers and fax number. By registering once, your subsequent visits will be even easier and more personal. When you sign in as a registered user, you'll be able to track the status of your order. When you check out, you will not have to fill in most of the required fields.

With your permission, we may also use this information periodically to send you information about our company, either by email or standard mail. This may include announcements about new features at our site or special offers that we think may be of interest to you. After you register and place an order using a check or credit card, with your permission, we may allow reputable third parties to provide you with offers we think you will find interesting. Unless you have ordered, we will not provide your registration information to any 3rd party, even if you have requested such offers. If you determine that you do not wish to receive this information, simply visit [My Account](https://checkout.hancocks-paducah.com/s.nl?sc=6&sc=6&whence=&origin=myaccount&login=T&vid=BmO4ZSmMAjo91M6m&chrole=17&ck=Ja6bHSmMAjg91FCi&cktime=166953&promocode=&promocodeaction=overwrite&sj=WIIHT4oRV059206TTHkWd6ySF%3B1549993786722&gc=clear) and select Update Profile to change your preferences.

Children Under the Age of 13

Like you, we at **www.hancocks-paducah.com** are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.

If we become aware that a subscriber is under the age of 13 and has signed up without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files.

Contacting **www.hancocks-paducah.com** about Children's Privacy or to control a child's access

**Hancock's of Paducah**  
Attn: Customer Service  
3841 Hinkleville Road  
Paducah , KY 42001  
270-443-4410  
800-845-8723  
fax: 270-442-2164 

Tell a Friend

If you enjoy your shopping experience at **www.hancocks-paducah.com** , which we believe you will, we encourage you to let others know through our Tell a Friend page. This form requires that you enter your friend's name and email address so that we can deliver the message, and your own name and email address so the recipient knows who sent the message. After the message has been sent, **Hancock's of Paducah** keeps no record of this personal information.

Product Purchase History

In order to help us better serve your needs and correctly target future promotions **Hancock's of Paducah** maintains a history of customers' past purchases. This information is used primarily to help us monitor the status of your orders, and secondarily to improve our marketing efforts, including the development of future merchandise offerings and the sending of promotions relevant to customers. With your permission, we will also allow reputable third parties to provide you with offers based on your purchase history. If you determine that you do not wish to receive this information and have registered at **www.hancocks-paducah.com** , simply visit [My Account](https://checkout.hancocks-paducah.com/s.nl?sc=6&sc=6&whence=&origin=myaccount&login=T&vid=BmO4ZSmMAjo91M6m&chrole=17&ck=Ja6bHSmMAjg91FCi&cktime=166953&promocode=&promocodeaction=overwrite&sj=WIIHT4oRV059206TTHkWd6ySF%3B1549993786722&gc=clear) and select Update Profile to change your preferences. If you are not a registered user, please [Contact Us]() to remove your name from our mailing list.

What about cookies and other types of tags?

"Cookies" are very small pieces of identification that your browser will place on your computer's hard drive. Cookies from the **Hancock's of Paducah** website are used to maintain your shopping cart and assist with the registration process. We use cookies only to ensure security. We do not store any personal information as a part of the cookie. We use your Internet Protocol (IP) address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Website and to gather broad (not individual) demographic information, such as how many orders we are receiving from your state. 

How can I access, update or correct my information?

Account Information

If you're a registered user at **www.hancocks-paducah.com** , you may access and/or change your account information- including name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, password, password hint, and opt-in/opt-out profile - by visiting the [My Account](https://checkout.hancocks-paducah.com/s.nl?sc=6&sc=6&whence=&origin=myaccount&login=T&vid=BmO4ZSmMAjo91M6m&chrole=17&ck=Ja6bHSmMAjg91FCi&cktime=166953&promocode=&promocodeaction=overwrite&sj=WIIHT4oRV059206TTHkWd6ySF%3B1549993786722&gc=clear) page.

Purchase History

If you're a registered user at **www.hancocks-paducah.com** , and would like to view the history of your past purchases, you may do so by visiting the [My Account]() page and clicking Order Status. Non-registered customers may request this information by clicking on [Contact Us]() , telephoning us at 1-800-845-8723, or writing to us at Hancock's of Paducah , 3841 Hinkleville Road , Paducah , KY , 42001 . While this information is available for viewing by customers, transaction history is a permanent part of the customer's record, and may not be changed.

Credit Card Information

Although Hancock's of Paducah does not maintain credit card number as a part of the customer profile, we do keep a record of the credit card number used for each Web transaction. This information must be maintained in case a customer requires a refund for an order. To request the credit card number you used for a particular order, you may click [Contact Us]() , telephoning us at 1-800-845-8723, or writing to us at **Hancock's of Paducah** , 3841 Hinkleville Road , Paducah , KY , 42001 . Upon verifying the identity of the requestor, **Hancock's of Paducah** will mail the credit card information to the credit card billing address on file, regardless of the medium used to submit the request. **Hancock's of Paducah** treats credit card information very carefully and will take every reasonable precaution to verify the identity of the requestor before sending this information.

How is my information protected?

We use Secure Socket Layer software (SSL) that protects your information whenever you place an order or access your account. The SSL encrypts all data you provide before it is sent to us. We also provide a variety of safeguards to ensure that no unauthorized person is allowed access to your data once you have provided it to us.

Choice/Opt-Out

If you do not wish to receive communications from us and have registered at the site, please indicate your preference to opt out by visiting [My Account](https://checkout.hancocks-paducah.com/s.nl?sc=6&sc=6&whence=&origin=myaccount&login=T&vid=BmO4ZSmMAjo91M6m&chrole=17&ck=Ja6bHSmMAjg91FCi&cktime=166953&promocode=&promocodeaction=overwrite&sj=WIIHT4oRV059206TTHkWd6ySF%3B1549993786722&gc=clear) and selecting Update Profile to change your preferences. If you are not a registered user, we offer several other options for removing your information from our database or electing not to receive future communications:

Click Contact Us and submit your request through this Website.

**Write to us at:**  
Hancock's of Paducah  
3841 Hinkleville Road  
Paducah , KY , 42001  
Telephone us from 8:00am - 6:00 pm CST, Monday - Friday days a week at:1-800-845-9207 Saturday 8:00 am - 3:00 pm CST .
